Guide to Tuli Kupferberg and Sylvia Topp Papers MSS.385
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VIII. Correspondence, 1949-2010, undated; 9 Linear Feet in 9 record cartons; 1.4 Megabytes
  - The Village Voice Submissions, 1996-1998 (Box 45, Folder 37)
  - Wagner, Gary, 1984-1989 (Box 45, Folder 38)
  - Wagner, Steve, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 39)
  - Waldman, Anne, 1986-1989 (Box 45, Folder 40)
  - Was It Good For Your Too? Requests, 1982-1984 (Box 45, Folder 41)
  - Weaver, Ken, 1969-2009 (Box 45, Folder 42)
  - Wehlau, Judith (Includes Artworks), 1965-1967 (Box 45, Folder 43-44, Box 326, Folder 4)
  - Weinstein, Ira, 1992 (Box 45, Folder 45)
  - Wilcock, John, 2007, undated (Box 45, Folder 46)
  - William, Michael, 1989 (Box 45, Folder 47)
  - Wilson, Peter, 2001-2007 (Box 45, Folder 48)
  - Wilson, Robert Anton, 1983-1986 (Box 45, Folder 49)
  - Winthrop, Nat, 2001 (Box 45, Folder 50)
  - Young, Izzy, 1990-1999 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - YouTube Mail, 2008 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Z., Bob (Re: Panic Button Press), 1992 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Zeitgeist Gallery, 1996 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Zelasnick (aka Zelasnic), Laura, 1982, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Zinn, Howard, 1995, 2006-2008 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - General (Re: Death), 1961-1999 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - General, 1950s (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - General, 1960s (Box 46, Folder 9-12)
  - General, 1970s (Box 46, Folder 13-16)
  - General, 1980s (Box 46, Folder 17-20, Box 47, Folder 1-5)
  - General, 1990s (Box 47, Folder 6-14)
  - General, 2000s (Box 48, Folder 1-11)
  - General, undated (Box 48, Folder 12-15)
- Series IX. Performance Props and Costumes, circa 1960s-2010; 25 Linear Feet in 1 manuscript box, 11 record cartons, 9 flat boxes, 1 oversize file folder, 1 oversize box, 2 musical instruments, 1 toy gun, 1 suitcase
  Materials in this series were grouped by the processing archivist into boxes by item type when possible.
  This series contains clothing, musical instruments, and toys used by Kupferberg in his performances with his band the Fugs, his performing group Revolting Theater, Revolting News television episodes, and solo performances. Army uniforms and helmets; flags; hats; small musical instruments; masks; novelty toys; toy soldiers; t-shirts with slogans; and toy weapons in this series date from the 1960s to 2010. Two of Kupferberg's handmade "erectorines" (a broomstick with hundreds of bottle caps nailed onto it), as well as a black suitcase he used to transport props to performances can also be found in this series.
  Items found too badly damaged or stained were deaccessioned by the processing archivist. Deaccessioned material includes bug-infested clothing, heavily stained t-shirts, rusted metal, melted candy, and broken, sharp objects.
  - Packaged Toys, circa 1960s-2010 (Box 291)
  - Costume Masks, circa 1960s-2010 (Box 292)
  - Toy Soldiers, Action Figures, circa 1960s-2010 (Box 293)
  - T-Shirts and Sweatshirt, circa 1960s-2010 (Box 294)
  - Fug and Kupferberg Cartoon T-Shirts, Sweatshirt, and Mug, circa 1960s-2010 (Box 295)
  - Clothing, circa 1960s-2010 (Box 330, Box 296)
  - Military Helmets and Hats, Baseball Caps, circa 1960s-2010 (Box 297)
  - Military Hats and Helmets, circa 1960s-2010 (Box 298)
  - Small Musical Instruments, circa 1960s-2010 (Box 299)
  - Military Gear and Toy Weapons, circa 1960s-2010 (Box 300, Box 290)
  - Cigarettes and Matchbooks, circa 1960s-2010 (Box 301)
  - Glasses Frames: Reading, Sun, Joke, circa 1960s-2010 (Box 302)
  - Military Jacket with Buttons, Pins, and Ribbons, circa 1960s-2010 (Box 303)
  - Black Suitcase with Clothing and Baby Doll, circa 1960s-2010; cuid8698 (Item mss.385.cuid8698)
  - Novelty Signs, Buttons (Fug and Political), circa 1960s-2010 (Box 305, Folder 1-3)
  - Erectorine (Musical Instrument) 1 of 2, circa 1960s-2010; cuid8699 (Box 328, Item mss.385.cuid8699)
  - Erectorine (Musical Instrument) 2 of 2, circa 1960s-2010; cuid8701 (Box 328, Item mss.385.cuid8701)
  - Wooden Toy Gun, circa 1960s-2010; cuid8700 (Box 329, Item mss.385.cuid8700)
  - Ceramic figures, dolls, pens, necklaces, cake-toppers, yo-yos, balls, circa 1960s-2010 (Box 306, Box 307, Box 308, Box 319, Box 320, Box 321)
  - Candle, Dishes, Toys, Stuffed Animals, circa 1960s-2010 (Box 309)
  - Small Signs, Record Albums, Slides, Badges, circa 1960s-2010 (Box 310)
  - Signs, Paper Uncle Sam, circa 1960s-2010 (Box 40, Folder 10)